let's do another quiz about history
predictors let's say we have a program
in which we have two nested Loops one I
goes from0 through 7 and then within it
we have a nested Loop of J goes from 0
through 7 let's say we do something that
doesn't have much branching behavior in
it this type of nested Loop structure is
very common when you have things like
matrices or even image processing in
particular for image processing it's
very common that for example compression
or decompression are working in blocks
of let's say 8 by8 pixels in this case
which will mean that there are Loops
like this all over the code let's say
that the code when it does this nested
Loop just does something else and then
very quickly comes back to it to do
another round of this so This Is Not
Just executed once the whole thing is
executed many many times if we are
building a history based predictor that
should do well on this code it needs at
least how many entries and each of these
entries should have how many bits of
history and how many two bit counters do
we need per entry as a result of this
history